this looks like a fun one if we know
this is six this is three and this is
four how do we solve for this y there's
something I really like called the
intersecting chord theorem if you take
the distance of the intersection to the
edge of the circle and call that a call
this distance D this distance n and this
distance y it will always be true that a
times n equals D times Y no matter how
much you move the chords around now we
could put a box around this and let's
move the label to the top so this is a
typical problem for one of these the six
three four and Y and to solve this it
would just be y times three equals six
times four which gives us 3y equals 24.
divide both sides by 3 and we get y
equals eight so this is the intersecting
chord theorem how exciting